humsurfer.com 2008-05-17

# Humsurfer privacy policy: Humsurfer

Humsurfer is the community news sharing site for global Indians. Get news recommended by others.  

**Humsurfer privacy policy**

At Humsurfer, we respect the privacy of the users of our website and services and are committed to protecting it. This policy was created to demonstrate our commitment to you and to help you understand it.

While registering with Humsurfer, we may collect personal information, including email addresses, to use the Humsurfer website and services, post a link to the Humsurfer website or submit questions, comments or bug reports. The purpose of collecting such information is to help diagnose problems with our servers, track movement and/or activities within our website and, if required, deny service in accordance with our Terms of Service. We may also collect information related to the referring URL, access times and browser type. We will not share our users' personal information and usage information, except with their consent, with third parties.

We use cookies to store and sometimes track information about our users so that we can offer and provide optimized and personalized services to them. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a user's browser from a web server and is eventually stored on a user's computer hard drive.

Optionally our users enable to receive communications from us to know our services updates.  We will never automatically send you information/offers you do not want. You must choose to receive them.

Visit your Humsurfer Settings to edit your profile and other information. When you're signed in, Humsurfer page headers will include a link to Settings. You can delete your Humsurfer account through your Settings.

Humsurfer reserves the right to modify all or some of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on our website. We will use information only in accordance with the Privacy Policy 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website or your dealings with this Humsurfer, you can send an e-mail to [privacy@humsurfer.com](mailto:privacy@humsurfer.com)
